[{"topicId":"20","id":"20000","langCode":"en","question":"rdCDUtpV0w5KErnkBotRwR0gP2fGsT/pou+I9NvM4m5XAzZETNJlLHIPp1GpLOh9HBTVyJQSx5sV4pWiQF8Hzw\u003d\u003d","answers":["colorfuler","colorful","as colorful","more colorful"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zjtkkKUp7H+H/djP0pb1kOaaC1h/mzOVYUYy7IXU8NouDIXvxjMGDFCbZ+39cp1fmZ0hTUBZXIVnzORa/aBjPOmblspt+8r4scbYvLdGBbr75h7MSjfUeyDJkZqdV1Ww2sSuor8K3DmQt0sSnxXTAGPGo2K2orsyfhyW4QMjKPtcMxMzMi6LUQ9JAgjxDltOXjt9PBuVAX+EmmmPCyS4uzWNVq/yttpdO4pg8e1t5xU"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20001","langCode":"en","question":"UCwZtIo/5sZ+c12B1xFYiPrliE6fx8Nt1ViZ8WatKSN7vbTaMBXg+Qy6B1vq1sCrXcR/xZauE7qVPe0Ab++whsfd4zFtzi+kdPrnCm3C4ik\u003d","answers":["dry than","drier","dry","dry as"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14f195ALHoWCD5bW+OkTod0tRSzcPWzzGUBhWZ/7eo9bXdgIyuAZedbk8xicmtpvR5GEoVDQjHXZ5fQlksbcEHBLr+rkRGGMVqaSnqwaV5XxM+u+08usVmxmcx8i58pPQ3ARszhSaLFJjFahUkQfdA89HL3RwwdvtQPi1HpiTbQIZ4gS5JrXBXdF6wqC7p4D/gB0vZTd7JTFyeXDFzSiCQo\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20002","langCode":"en","question":"+uy1cCcrPf/GnHzrJrIdmEJa/qWwwv5DgPHxd0AzL4pRjbYsBf/RBxkB86hLdDD800yDwc3IQclyzx1rGP94Og\u003d\u003d","answers":["more good","well","good","as good"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x121s7DlL3lxKqMWuE2pPyAhVN6YIUL6Mw23ufhezWPm3VjfOiheClw+epcsYwv3catwLqTMttyF8OiMD+AVUu8XxR6cLu9ALlcDP5j3nCENlY4Rui8JEHvBDI1n0CRWUxRlDm6ihaXiDT5/HGHfaRqwPLMyqdD1vcQ9rtHxu3I35lm/Y6SEd4soISRo3eIOLtFT4GiVpe1y+D7mYE/LAjzOEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20003","langCode":"en","question":"DGhTdxhKDggch+5HYtM7SpekvniNyfDU4bImGNXXXhi0YiB2mLaVDNkmCPl9Lr/E/5liG818SLATGrybaN5T/EqnmPWJiMMG+Wa9iWEabSugwXdibYGlgr5gGNfq5TGS","answers":["worse","bad than","bad as","bad"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w3CpoNoVga48BTaWkyM0aQtRSzcPWzzGUBhWZ/7eo9bXdgIyuAZedbk8xicmtpvR5GEoVDQjHXZ5fQlksbcEHBLr+rkRGGMVqaSnqwaV5XxM+u+08usVmxmcx8i58pPQ3ARszhSaLFJjFahUkQfdA89HL3RwwdvtQPi1HpiTbQIZ4gS5JrXBXdF6wqC7p4D/gB0vZTd7JTFyeXDFzSiCQo\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20004","langCode":"en","question":"qJna5UkMjpHRiKVi25wgjP+vngdViCSNRTN3JlsbPLOEDaOYgHeK+ZuHLgmTbyvhFycFbhGSjadZGPgr5zpoCA\u003d\u003d","answers":["as carefully","more carefully","less carefully","carefully"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1//6hcXoLMngzKa/q8zEkkr2gBqyvHYjlQ8XiQ/O3DNV/lUswkd615ZRKR7k0pMXGXAY6Lt/mnyo6Ez4XXEZbLQWQL0cC6kxcFC2b2/RK/L71dR/hAI3C6YbcSQIrdf6sMtIsZcGNeIpOHQTJlZQNL9SkhAa6rC1f19I7mlbYtuaW2/6whBv9yq0qmQd42nzmudSt4jZy4wT4F9HB0Njuak4Q82W5kO90h2oYXaF6gJI"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20005","langCode":"en","question":"lBKWFaN5eGL9169063l0GUaX1N2k3bnqpoehTsX5onyhOv0c9ne5U7B1AZaTMLxWXlL4OHevEUjSMaHr7D4pHw\u003d\u003d","answers":["more much money as","much money as","as much money as","as much money than"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17+plgKji2nA8hMFCXrA5pkFL5D2pGvph0YNeOQywAcaVqRJZGVCoQuDUzFc9iDLQ8n7e33R+5rQZugZ0cOy+8W1vQMB/KN49eOI69fs2SGefpLan50I6x71fhvHhAoGoACI2e9P8cAN6T3w8y9VbV6e4KJpGn4CdpE6bReVxFIMhA/FeeWTw6V+a0SRIv0C9hHjSQU4TAw3lb3h95Ul8BVn2qJRO47PSN9Zte8nF6+kjL8xzHUc5VwDmil6LLgD7KViWWyfvL452kwfSMlXO0U2YQh7Cqc6oj78lgVEQXeshr/e1uAcYFKNLKZ03tCKx6SSNZ8WtVc3TA18h8hOy3t7iiLRhdQZZVaeOMYL5SURIMMnaCa1huGoxOijZrl7/oSCjOrP2aMYUXPs3ugB0iQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20006","langCode":"en","question":"EsYklG2MY3UMpRtMJr76lmlkP+TUBYpj7hPzWJP0E4IsC0MctNcdtq8GEH8Q/Kf78oIDPwoCktJlgucd+kuzFQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["more many people","many people","as many people","as much people"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11b1haYs8QQvgLGunMZwUTnLLWzGRzMA/izrnERXOB2QtpKiV6YsxUgiaui/V9s8Kt1EQ1juFvwWuCmFfwTh2geuOhfwVzsoEk3rrEVTpbbSBuJiNyIVOySmUCJulCH2efmyZv97fTgy7WomNWQBv+XGYebIY8IaXwd5eIbWTClXXidhHbx7fIO4c1EMu+LbR1HTwVZDaq3Noo9mY1ix+k4JTBuNGlboUE/pOwcD55udu/JjXhHWtL1EC/iJO4AjnlpKkM/n9qKOAl+rmkLfznARtNs3sTtxagV4ZcHbbw5GQBnnkzz2nrjC9Qe0V0E/2FjrqNRQHIgxFmTY22IV75h4AqpBHwQGM6TNik6OvyiSNewQgJ9RL9YnZsMBgVq+vwCLjIqqbWl84Hhi5Wn92R0\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20007","langCode":"en","question":"oLcqHtT/jf4cl3MwWoH97Xhj+H6a5z9KMzsRzjakh3QStfDhsbDw+oEpC/kX0nEpnsyQ0sO3lgTmemCWRmCsqXpspiPnjg2JunVo40NgfDOEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["as much than 3,000 times","more much as 3,000 times","as much as 3,000 times","3,000 times"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17+plgKji2nA8hMFCXrA5pn3kFQOLmuO0ZnxVXugsWhELUUs3D1s8xlAYVmf+3qPW13YCMrgGXnW5PMYnJrab0eRhKFQ0Ix12eX0JZLG3BBwS6/q5ERhjFamkp6sGleV8TPrvtPLrFZsZnMfIufKT0Mb8iok7QEUKofYKZFxYGslZOvTbfEGpwiEJxI+AHXD6fGYwSs+5GUz5JF97Mr0jPI+61SYqma/bVN/XlOffPVKfqH0h/yoCvAeSmMJiyV8mpmXtQjvc40LgVsV2sDKcDmS57FORzrG/Cu4nXPtD59I1fT68BLvdyMvCX7Rv3UfmcsDXiGvbbbqAXwM9F00b0/msAFxLQyA51D2W2LpVo+rdPHo96hSyFBtkjboNMBO0+ZAQk5kOtqcNbUfq8K2LV+cQaH14AV0KNRsl5dWGaGQ70Zu+RZlTJkePIaejORZm6/hLXD0Nb1Qc7SgRRljdoIPLMyqdD1vcQ9rtHxu3I35lm/Y6SEd4soISRo3eIOLtFT4GiVpe1y+D7mYE/LAjzOEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20008","langCode":"en","question":"sFpVyp+cUq5ZSK37yzYOrSs629SaDDsPexCekTbrhMni57gFgHa3TgHx8rY8Lmhg","answers":["as many than 50 people","more many as 50 people","50 people","as many as 50 people"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11b1haYs8QQvgLGunMZwUTkg9eSKoyniPhphEv4v9EQqAwzaAwusLlLvvNrGjtBR5PXzJ/2tWg2Kk/uiqjEWlHrnlh91mBvM/V1mE0a/LmEZXaecWt9dWEjCZYWF5AEvTpHugmRF5/vGQTA9/4sy+dsI0MK2gtveuNZ+hImO4jOq0xB00kcHJyHXeekr7x6sbGzNnZoA31WIvGx0avMCNwFXZTBCPSxjNMSOjUmNNVTDzLHeK0XWC5tP80RtHDOzI+a7hZA+MH5EL0rFL4YdavUv21zO6Tx1ougXFlnLGjZgxIHPxe1vq2qFGnEA2qg6P5OFuZaIkd5h2lMavRtC0Vtto6WCDZu66KdMOlF4zfWucZ1cBHf1txirwY7W0lid02F3nGTeXOUjld+IoyhcMK/u/RYdg8RlcZ1lnWDt6lZnJDAOQcjAlhNwZsFsI73oCsm3iVJZ1o6psEOG16SmiCek31hcsPv4ULneOoJDKb39neYZEX3LNa24YqqKyc/OWPlKSskKJVfBVsF90WR2UrY\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20009","langCode":"en","question":"ZePJb/QgI1HSuyuNxPuRCFB7T/C90llYdEkdvH3AZprsMc0buVB4NBEMj+OFIjxJzVkQAobEHsCSiLZN0dFZf1/MvZSwQdLM0fAH8OQ+eK8\u003d","answers":["as heavy","heavy","more heavy","not as heavy"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1z74BKzd3X+IpB9vzXFWKElcpkNx4Q2PVKoomrGa5gCl/lUswkd615ZRKR7k0pMXGXAY6Lt/mnyo6Ez4XXEZbLQWQL0cC6kxcFC2b2/RK/L71dR/hAI3C6YbcSQIrdf6sDjtklzO0PuFkzfGdjZHnehr/+F8Akl/bfJZJB6DXmW/jOSMXzjw56nA1RM01rBgLhCqESSKb1w/9CM5LLohQUkGkuvwak/J5ETreXxLelsjubvSzZ9ARBziklrrvS4f7Xku0sgin4OX47gPdcvnlPiHLn3aVwuF9C/DPcXJt1GmHtgy4fHjWv693kcl7siyn297AXi2pYVFdMn2zeg+Sx4\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20010","langCode":"en","question":"SlfAq0Q46Qi4Zr8KO9oby5ioj3/sMAhwAoiUC+joLTbWNxKhmU3HiA0v5zoRHR37NKECzFZe3p964QoXPxfUi3epukRZBm6Nexx0jO2N464\u003d","answers":["as well","not as well","more well","well"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19qU9/UWUjlZFp3JGE3hXTImiDdxEoYhjqJx2XmrmdU1VjfOiheClw+epcsYwv3catwLqTMttyF8OiMD+AVUu8XxR6cLu9ALlcDP5j3nCENlY4Rui8JEHvBDI1n0CRWUxVYOjGseBM0Mzl6EwI4ROxhwqY0zPiDiASdZ+JwhsVV0Pz+f2VhSOrt8kV6j56MIdmTN/oLTmoMhAaGLfxcq91r0jhzTFuX/NkZDP2l0CIPy0dHX4tO40HT/NYL+AsR119NAqepsFxIfBzRtsjEdmdRwsi2eT2PCU0jmW6CRaEqkECLViYIyMwodw6o7Ejli3HP+BzgVzMvhpkAqXpMfUyc\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20011","langCode":"en","question":"btwx+N6lI7y7HwxbOFNxmIQAHmcdaOlJxtssBQj+7jOpE4IuMGPQTld6vx0hVJUrgmN14LaDv48UovCzHAYcWaY7tG+ZsEqUjfQaoU7dDut+CvrECKvE7ulhZJ+jZO3g","answers":["quite as easy","more quite as easy","quite easy","not quite as easy"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18jO2h7iuKIqsA69ctwlnBgih5nJ8aE3gUeJ5pWmJXTdzWRQQZsKVI6gkviuWx68HYT9b0WZPCJdQqDbltDduk1cEwpZdCYlVDeD03uu5w5i94Qdo6RYzbwEn4Fo2XXIlAKnXsaLjEMlcXPW7cQXv3ylscvEzlAvyA0xjjrtljJpvGImmIkjWhJjWCeCfB9h/oYGXdX9LqxT1P3/3K26gmsgUWc+I4PCHffIiandmUf0J+D8Fk6E9S4rKpINpG3tA7Mlti/YT6nRvrvKn1Jzcq0MT3pwEQSVmBHdxSVl1N9N70r9Y9Yb5fTZF9Q6QASESk5kyfFpidwSrZnSKUTHut7/koIdzkhMuY/7RaH6cVP200Cp6mwXEh8HNG2yMR2Z1HCyLZ5PY8JTSOZboJFoSqQQItWJgjIzCh3DqjsSOWLcc/4HOBXMy+GmQCpekx9TJw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20012","langCode":"en","question":"SXHuAh/quS4cI3U1SWzM3XHnlktWt5z6T4+T7+5DGQeEywYnDNrlmAWqK/mY3GfZ","answers":["not nearly less comfortable","not nearly as comfortable","not comfortable","not nearly more comfortable"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x165d0JKPJihfxp/fRFS7vJiXoexuKbiSfHIHn+pZpufVlQPeuHaglMnvTQPeUbUbOAjsApp4mb2IdEIx8Qo4kQZtJu+2wKPj2HIlFa64Sy4B7LSiCe2ytZ8HllknZN9rDZreBTJt2P18nT+yiZcEkBh26Zgrq+JnUPbBJOsd9+deR2FAefX2FEnEkfiMYPIWh6Vc8+kW3XiVjRNPLlWhl46BcjBRwCwclOrs3/RmntQagr9Q/lACWfHlk6N4ezIy/ZosewqLIgZuVHt5uiFD3StltINd68sYLpItXGf0ojtebxuB5jO/sBMbkQohE5I5nx96mL2yyaIjbH1ls6bQw1L5GuKDD+utYLTQder/A6rPWOuo1FAciDEWZNjbYhXvmHgCqkEfBAYzpM2KTo6/KJI17BCAn1Ev1idmwwGBWr6/AIuMiqptaXzgeGLlaf3ZHQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20013","langCode":"en","question":"C0SFniuF3axxwron/5ep+Y3JATo0oyLb2zy2YEQledXy55YeHFqlxaagVuxt1ybh3s08t/cZd9OQfbwve9jzMR6TbCTwwyslEvth5rkNemc\u003d","answers":["not less hard","not more hard","not much more hard","not so hard"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/WjX9zlp/j11ml40+vD+i++38SVHQMXH9aa62ZjOfatuDIXvxjMGDFCbZ+39cp1fmZ0hTUBZXIVnzORa/aBjPOmblspt+8r4scbYvLdGBbr75h7MSjfUeyDJkZqdV1WwwJwnflQx7kmb2o/TqdS5dy7znvtaz42fDFG+Scu1haWCa7occYgm6YyH4pdBVGX6X+9xMyMmNMN9ldw0ZDrR/bFTR6hy5EvLFU4OwC5cVKS4omMON2paTj50KmT4VznkeLX7iK8BSHWMnjQuxHg4Z64KWlgslfORCzPSXvDVoLcNP7lGqfCdkcM7UYeRjrEgn03e4soX324z6Vy0QYwhDt1DN4kPYLs0ee4U/4NirkSQnJWDOjoKTtpvNCWtcJ4jilivYEiAtiPkbycfiu0lGwUgghZaAID2A4vw6ukHvHue+fJW/83lRJFDhY5mxlLVQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20014","langCode":"en","question":"VeQT47/coJseLDUPSYFKQ2ObjjsiEb7fjcnlO0aDjnyjHlJJCeDkG1ROGlHvfvWt","answers":["more","as","so","the same"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17zGa4H2qIjB9Y4ANUTYc2zX1luafRsm37wgVyjjnWhAUjkWCoCaTFVX+X38cFmxl/lEpwm/DJfuLYxMDLZFTt5cD8vD272kRDqhJJPIP8XDx4BRm1opAGeB0bv1TvU+NVKSEBrqsLV/X0juaVti25pbb/rCEG/3KrSqZB3jafOa51K3iNnLjBPgX0cHQ2O5qThDzZbmQ73SHahhdoXqAkg\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20015","langCode":"en","question":"E5XIOXuMCpcPtIwxNpgc85eVG1uP/+Q8kRUovey8BksY6tptIwfY5RqZ9QcxG/1p6KMVOzP6NZaA8DePRIFP4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["the same","more","so","less"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17zGa4H2qIjB9Y4ANUTYc2zX1luafRsm37wgVyjjnWhAUjkWCoCaTFVX+X38cFmxl/lEpwm/DJfuLYxMDLZFTt5cD8vD272kRDqhJJPIP8XDx4BRm1opAGeB0bv1TvU+NVKSEBrqsLV/X0juaVti25pbb/rCEG/3KrSqZB3jafOa51K3iNnLjBPgX0cHQ2O5qThDzZbmQ73SHahhdoXqAkg\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20016","langCode":"en","question":"e2to/IpzLsx6ADhT691s3uXs512OgcoqB15Va8Gl7zbg83Zr4Nr5F6cPJoq94UWn1XWzBJtxCPSpfjcxXI1DgVSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["more","less","the same","as"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17zGa4H2qIjB9Y4ANUTYc2zX1luafRsm37wgVyjjnWhAUjkWCoCaTFVX+X38cFmxl/lEpwm/DJfuLYxMDLZFTt5cD8vD272kRDqhJJPIP8XDx4BRm1opAGeB0bv1TvU+NVKSEBrqsLV/X0juaVti25pbb/rCEG/3KrSqZB3jafOa51K3iNnLjBPgX0cHQ2O5qThDzZbmQ73SHahhdoXqAkg\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20017","langCode":"en","question":"qFeax0OSNIHSrN2wOk1Kb/VxGOnSv+nD/U2wqv3GtvaK2JbEXOKTahsHbURwIIWC0QpDMlLmyOJLORfZuq4wsQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["fastest","as fast","faster","fast"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yI2AQDMQkkWcM9++SzIGKixfsc+0s/t2NeZJxmYLgW1vOwZ+Ni63qsUD3/FiH2f9RQs+EpFh4Ee5tFMuMqLy9++CaPs+rjPU9m8alcgWnLEDUXM9uMUXfI28uTmchdEBPsEvk6S7xTFWvTeE13PeYRjniWIJFJEs8mEDmNqrLq6O5smIoYCKG306n7IVeT9dxtD51ThJgJhYAApz4v0szkoAPN2Xh7z433WNx/SzHpnijAzyKIDa9IIO8lz5/7LIRU81JsUA7Bh+7Zf1m6dZsD6uyklN2+quvgTrtlw6UjFXFlYAPHS80F6YPNCm16trwXuRu5a4qbQSEh2f9uEj6dJwCuPz80T0Mal60IEM69rIrwH4l0486ysZozkh3zv8zJA1YdiT4AHCIKg0KCP3ivwmwKK3eaami4cRnJXJTyQmiomtlaZeWXFrwTEYVKf5QB0vZTd7JTFyeXDFzSiCQo\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20018","langCode":"en","question":"rp0zmrt4WbSBQmcXGoaIN7ccKO8MJbgc6e52NfsQdnLl4ocES8JxvOA/cjFuvalXvjsVNh8nrgpIESkoqRIBOnuucVgUxxkm3PkZVlP7/5E\u003d","answers":["earlier","early","earliest","as early"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+2nbDHSMCls/1auSHe2TxAnGJUtG/F7o5YyvkMzOwTZ5pLJXqMIw9rCsdjyIk5iwTdwiCSc31r2+cw3Av9gs+9fPYd0UcEgN0oeVPUywGtVUfBmzNnkrlr5oi+IvS/jhxpQm2Nl0hbSji7cWzbjUbmLgh6g4Hd6czXM4FYKP7Hsk1kmXccLANd1AMPGeyoTzUilipAGk5urjsmiaPQxsXRYq9Z5U+s/lhpkmZujdlMUNr42Dxj4HRMFHf+s1EPHKCTGkBXjffYVWlNtStQw3V6tYAUu0kbGd/By58m9wzqrVeB0HDmiLXQzmweVLDfqUtIvGfxkFwhw6ePEx/i8whVhDNsUL9IuyU59UG4MNVrSBqM6tBJOFsTHT+LSNlPIq0VX8YksyMQQEHYSiUyoMt8qSAm/PqiF+FBBYFenER96qmOjGhpqRwHLT83fx6xgr/+uCR+2Ymt/4jSgJoU2Y3g4Q82W5kO90h2oYXaF6gJI"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20019","langCode":"en","question":"GboPKSXjE2VXtdqOhXjWBVFzYPv4GOlOAO8Bs4Tcy7lUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["interested","as interested","more interested","most interested"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18HdOfBh1DMS/Od2VLLiZk4qDKA3hPNmHVHmnLozmdB+cKSzaZsQbybZVPjBhZo51HoftiFC6O/Tf8amUxDLzM687Bn42LreqxQPf8WIfZ/1ALC+64SoPKieWRTnw2BylBASNEL1e9vIarHZ2dmmXX72/HZKmThpWJIRXHQUUXNZ3IiiV+g/j+pFA4NdLNmkBWM8HWTsPPhz3XczmpnTNsamPpXw0e+1qO88X+JBxRCL9CEViZG1zZogx04E+tcTXoBLCoyUapsOcjqqVQWEn+5mLOubBKWM15iMLYLSC7dcNwtynEQUVw30rVhBW0C66nYcxr+PECA/85XIkqUg2X9Roe/rc4lEEk/Jeh4UJ2uqYfCIW0ajd/nPgTCVK65TbTwmj1K0leo9cRqNKbvPRs0pmtPfswAp8Kk3PwIIHxH5WQ95RFyoByAzF07OBgD0MChjXDsZHetAQBWZyVSfNXA7gN09Zcai4Fs2PUuDGqXW"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20020","langCode":"en","question":"lsZ8fOYMMVKZ/KEJEdG7eiIcOw2GYgtA1qW+nMpTn627Wbk5iAVQPVtzCsmT8QIx1u1T9nxIlijmLwOtmp2b/G/tTV7hVcHYXIvP6i/nq+s\u003d","answers":["as popular","popular","less popular","popularer"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18WX5ZysAzZE+PcDmfriqubN0p2HKHL1qDAKo23OMSSx027qe8RPeB5/lI49o8FsxIuW6LGzeeUrDwPW0XNtuuoV/9k01dKoUzVCkfCiujvd/Q1zRjl/HyjXFxPVzusKCdeEsTcwMHRGqK5p9zD1nNRiFZOf4mg9yJDvCgORd78Lz+5cJpmphxyLuIGz7l5iNImWjYVYRnrewqafxEXYz79iqjeCauiVJPOjEwRnv1zOYwLW0+lmoo4CmicDpOImRr5bt9ACYGF9WC7lIa6xRjMUHGOcqJ9s6jH2evurSV5qjPOUsMj4G61YZ9d+7xYEYOtyjPcLyIhqWv1vy8yVIYHbhQ6H3RNY09QOcCdhCOsDnlq0qhhqqt/1J2Wng/Xh+BKccietZ5Hw2ZsV2CnXU1dDinXN0OwzvHuTxhH2Pac73CO3L8g8dEEDD8leOLgO30V2uiC761dgP2Mzv/W6c/mEpaN3tPkKGa4N0myQVg5A"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20021","langCode":"en","question":"QUxR+rPZHzeYEHWKyvGbNg4ylvw6BtS9T7D1ABsiXcOptlCWtySNodM6l7ZfiqlTSWjLwQFL9Oz2n18eriYD6g\u003d\u003d","answers":["clever","more clever","as clever","cleverer"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+oKyWvNkxleDKdpygn43uf/IKn6a5V1tWOI8vKgPbw4LtdJzgiggZ4sOpqxxegZdl/ZDR/ZSXHPlJpMeCXkCrPW2SylQoO5b24bNtMJ6223+vwEguSnQPmVh9ciE2+3D94yeKS5phtZSb+QNmid7oh2PMX+Y3T+JUuYQCcerKriv8es/zwJW5qEVWu2IAQgey8X7eenqypWTkDLzvRmiEx/pbhWFlvOKN5FWV+yA8cnu2lAmMXg6M4DBAR4WdjYfJzXuTcnxPyFnc+U5kmwl1VZzFmR9qVw2CR9JKq2i2pbWmqvBos3lU+HGF9y6UaoxG/tEjouPNeuXvhphkz/eImv5AKuIMT9iTeFq195Qe4KL/O/40gLnyCU+43QPaviOkdszqUO0fUyGJugt/Uf2xzonjcN8PiYVv19TJnN+A8BNub76shQS8K9zFCu2XeTeWmotM90GbQnOhNoP//Vktk++rjjj2dQTLk5geD/9idi"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20022","langCode":"en","question":"6F2xudbDGgcyKbNmjkfFermILtxMidCtZpgTmFWP3veKdDHaKMLj+i4ls/+qp6Qa","answers":["narrower","as narrow","narrow","more narrow"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11HeVuVZcW36Rn8qK098Drb/IKn6a5V1tWOI8vKgPbw4LtdJzgiggZ4sOpqxxegZdl/ZDR/ZSXHPlJpMeCXkCrPW2SylQoO5b24bNtMJ6223+vwEguSnQPmVh9ciE2+3D94yeKS5phtZSb+QNmid7oh2PMX+Y3T+JUuYQCcerKriv8es/zwJW5qEVWu2IAQgey8X7eenqypWTkDLzvRmiEx/pbhWFlvOKN5FWV+yA8cnu2lAmMXg6M4DBAR4WdjYfJzXuTcnxPyFnc+U5kmwl1VZzFmR9qVw2CR9JKq2i2pbWmqvBos3lU+HGF9y6UaoxG/tEjouPNeuXvhphkz/eImv5AKuIMT9iTeFq195Qe4KL/O/40gLnyCU+43QPaviOkdszqUO0fUyGJugt/Uf2xzonjcN8PiYVv19TJnN+A8BNub76shQS8K9zFCu2XeTeWmotM90GbQnOhNoP//Vktk++rjjj2dQTLk5geD/9idi"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20023","langCode":"en","question":"2syYKxQVl+XZ2x434/9FfokKvLVUI5TEAlyVRFZPkjaY7N9p1C8glw5QFZBoctT5Tms0DB2IOPtn60youexQxA\u003d\u003d","answers":["usefuler","as useful","more useful","useful"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19yBYpCDIPVD66sT9E1ZWk5cawdNhgqlno2Pjg6VrpjxWp0gW7NlCuvpm6xHIr528LGili61gl11zp0bBn9r/yUZh9JRDT8SzR/EyjVeaCl0Qff8SgfUzvMdWkkvTiANxld/6nodZ81JHJ+9n6TU82xOiRpvy2zNN53pUe+AO1ZUITWkJyGpQxTcSOYMWC6EaraDP0GuRrmR74UNy5ksRXUCduC0EIXhShSNzgGXbzIcRoqb0f2VzvYmHw1dMoeiEBDfG5MJj603GmzOUCh+yolCZ6hH2HqI214w3xGLf7iOjPOUsMj4G61YZ9d+7xYEYOtyjPcLyIhqWv1vy8yVIYHbhQ6H3RNY09QOcCdhCOsDnlq0qhhqqt/1J2Wng/Xh+BKccietZ5Hw2ZsV2CnXU1dDinXN0OwzvHuTxhH2Pac73CO3L8g8dEEDD8leOLgO30V2uiC761dgP2Mzv/W6c/mEpaN3tPkKGa4N0myQVg5A"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20024","langCode":"en","question":"HQ+NDo+pSphoKu3ol6h49/3U0sddyh9CrvuWsVEpofYE7E2MCEyVJW+DIima9dCp","answers":["patienter","patient as","more patient","as patient"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1y2QXlswsnweu9jF+SzCxzFXXU7uAgWBFeQJhS+g99a6027qe8RPeB5/lI49o8FsxIuW6LGzeeUrDwPW0XNtuuoV/9k01dKoUzVCkfCiujvd/Q1zRjl/HyjXFxPVzusKCdeEsTcwMHRGqK5p9zD1nNRiFZOf4mg9yJDvCgORd78Lz+5cJpmphxyLuIGz7l5iNImWjYVYRnrewqafxEXYz79iqjeCauiVJPOjEwRnv1zOYwLW0+lmoo4CmicDpOImRr5bt9ACYGF9WC7lIa6xRjMUHGOcqJ9s6jH2evurSV5qjPOUsMj4G61YZ9d+7xYEYOtyjPcLyIhqWv1vy8yVIYHbhQ6H3RNY09QOcCdhCOsDnlq0qhhqqt/1J2Wng/Xh+BKccietZ5Hw2ZsV2CnXU1dDinXN0OwzvHuTxhH2Pac73CO3L8g8dEEDD8leOLgO30V2uiC761dgP2Mzv/W6c/mEpaN3tPkKGa4N0myQVg5A"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20025","langCode":"en","question":"OPmpB8PUvTkNIJTBkM1hY8RSK9M7A0MPRc0+B18Oj+S1WVtnsryhk929trtQdc/t","answers":["more long holiday","longer holiday","long holiday","less long holiday"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19cjaVe7vJOfpQAwr2MNjpJPeN/rRWkUe/HR1EjHCnYW3LdjtuBNacmzCcBErfapwBLZ7iGEtgeexq3uG6aSA/LjqVtJwGA6m2G0+4yEBHJpIuhyWiUOY/BYEGyqyzOZ8OxYWoMxQs1QuQUgBaykFbTXG2qkJk7J+fo42TwV2phX7hxZ+yorpwsTJv0urL20jXnuwTGAZfj5h8dBYdOFursfLWLe34v+erxALW6+PdpeMZoWzkiEzLXLp1t96/8/gC4Wnmu/eBbN2R+vYHOq9R2fOsIjSiOTYPG4L/KDEIqCaXPkCmsAAvYs3IbcG1xvc3g88CaafKg5HszxDtIqHFpVYiZz6QKSiODD8GrF1OKMQJVCtQH72nFm03IsaUuYYDY1U999Q8YpKlMjb2Kp4g62JyKM5/tlW6zMWT6QV3fMKE9iZEOSOvPgVW0GSzFV9KQQIbIaHIce4NuzpqLIad8Ai4yKqm1pfOB4YuVp/dkd"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20026","langCode":"en","question":"E1iaX/uaviGyeO4utCNq//4z+7H2AasoUn778vBqA+ziSTIJV+WAHuGrJ3+twzSAnSlWnsNKxRVKJqn7xu3BmtYGC6yHHYZ5tWqcdNVKWGvb6EA2etK9FEaVzWacsH7raKp4CbibjCiYhDRHsJdfZg\u003d\u003d","answers":["as fast","fast","fastest","faster"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16aFYjbCOQ8CmEWh76kdvYEZComMlOLgbemZE+nwdlr47xUr71lsN2JariMUa5N3vJ2JyHrZ3K9SfElOIDciEPGowxj/mLcvH0fDWOVbkXqkr5dYcbEjs91tZq/RzhLTLfAxoxP+3Rrf1DwcUzCFHs5sUzsE0C0JdyY/h708NDL7bOtQhkD+eGo1RtnzUHKZ9ukWt/vwEROojlyZ21UQqyLbY3a8uhB5H8gHADfGlLKR5y9lxvfcM/7g3mOcAqKedtmZMlbnjzBJa/XHV5TvWzMNXEHpXC2i3ca5LwZA6ScAy3d1L1KUX7y2NjuJGU6aV1Ai9/4ct68u/wOvFjrZrH/oPcFJX3c59R1rMC+fc4ethDqXDmRusxfZqlPxAPeUWw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20027","langCode":"en","question":"fzOHhEUVpQusQ6gTomN3YGV486s+ZE/NykUPM1B52k9i0aqrmVfg1Zfk/0YclPYw5vk+NhIJupUmsVedT8ms+g\u003d\u003d","answers":["most frightening","more frightening","frightening","as frightening"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+fdnr5AEqNiRXlbhX/0TfSSfDn8LkaTcLclEL+fO5fnwzs0vFzcZT0mSyYJ54ipIFSthwdrGykzeJxlQijHBHw30EONC7/Xpc1n4jvKNo6gJj0cW0+jDiYfjDFruRqlpqa3hzG6yzJhaz+IGm2ZY28Am/ds90mABW+2EuCQiGT2m4u2V6Poru67UPDLTvh0gqBp+OkWOcDvF+KJdevQ/bRHS3PFpdjXhS5gZqi26QixkaylhgdxRuC8yg9sQuUrzaak0kKlR3DbqI2+0YbH8RUrr5ejLpG5OS8BEvL9R+G4V2EieWIkdzO1doCsRRTTZ91xYlw5s4hYb2Og8OOptDo6FPaKc7uPUAih12rggPyztXegrUyuJnv8kBuw2JpMQlMO7jY1mkBTaYKndJxknDE\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20028","langCode":"en","question":"cOFqG7F0PmARLzWgr5jj+OqBmEXEF1Mw/uo9UrFJjo4n9jdp783dyfWB5RJVbfZoJ2fcGkVPpjGfc58NC2BnpclDsXYaQenPugxhHnWtw/c\u003d","answers":["as tall skyscraper","taller skyscraper","tallest skyscraper","tall skyscraper"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13t1nGlJZbFn+1iGpFw0ngx9aseE2oPXge7MJl27YidiMBdzXLQgsTT5+bxVOCa+o86vKAwng1r5oAZjuw0duOvEudNqH0ztAidG7EE7lg3G71fhsWmqUawzOjpQSYJbscOnEDXh6Jaf0PsKgdfnCqcCKAT6TJlHP9WpcmLP5zJlxInw7J+EXrswwuPgCPljAeFvgb3h4Sjq5mMePTHhXypMKQC9rJVFlLKI0dRDBfPRX9z2wryjE9pYGyO2XB881gJ2Eo71k91NqHQXG0tyWtXsFVuRGVdR9xYdJkaFmNXJ7wQOKFMuf3y9KLkJADlGvjORQfA8Ppq+vA/NtywVZQt8gAlWCjPpeVdTekM/Mn//zrWlsy1YTZwR6GKj8Ugvpo5Zv0HYndsKNa6l0jgFEjE\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20029","langCode":"en","question":"AG+g9uZ3DcwiCSRRm+a1cotaIYCd23HjIG7TrfEzhwMVnqJEH1fGHrEwictJeAcARH45oBSoSrp7AavYJDEpTNnDwpCvDDJcFqzU4lxz5LA\u003d","answers":["older/younger","old/younger","oldest/youngest","old/young"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wfExyQUn3qiGH3/6odgDrAyUWET5BeYqgJWJeXsY+PPJBHPBf4BWEhymo1O0Glmap6fnXQTiY/BYlGQgcli04WLbHBHJTI9DyaT9dtfqWCdgJoWfWFWfDZhwogk8SckNU0zY9vPnopVA3H7UMT+sEJ1kQPvUOeE49QufkSW2GEUFtDxwZa6ohcTqr66jPsTiLZaq0iUFOERcYi8IN3iKNtRx3Rfs9Kq79pGuXbzcvqZnauL3fCA8WWn0RwUAP8XLrIZ6Y9mFiOcu9x91Sq8QC8ADq0m+kQrBBP5gjBTl/1CRIO8vB6Uji9CJXFtcNyEzjKOL/RXk9iDz8WgjQLG6sHzNiyP5oUp5TJJPKkHh55Auq1upUYUd6cqLRI9qkipJSk5KyXUaeZSP81RBrKyJoE\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20030","langCode":"en","question":"+GmkKOYBURlxXXjsyu9t42t6oLrVixmcXL0O89UNPyZf0QCuiAk1SR/x97EBfMP3","answers":["as bad play","worst play","worse play","bad play"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19OcyxN7u+Up1OkAHpGOf2AWxSiGwgiKKn8Yjhh16IqCMi7K24OHeEs1RkPhC2azp0BfPVrUC1bQb1LqEKqIAGTZhMxNqPvwMa5vK00HrgsdiZB6nCEqIKbC58OnNOH62URZ72nXm95/VLc8wtJ7ezbi3jkVjCin9iOFfaHnUdb8oTkD6Qk6YEj41Ntv0/jZ6YSIGvbfECjJE6mrQYZ9HCSi2R0a490u2ThpusiybwFB65uzNGTzSO23CJEk5dUngWlz5AprAAL2LNyG3Btcb3Pf6XOCR5+OrUruXohCcuBAgcSLfpOw2Lxhu2b8W0TK0jJA1YdiT4AHCIKg0KCP3isoM9eZwEMdQts+EXtwKYMBOxNE4OoxV652J7mHY0EOALVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20031","langCode":"en","question":"RBu6gnu3xSRNLvESZi5IpWB3lkRv7l/6Y5UsxQBVrkz+g/dft260EJNd1IYwfj27/aNm7w71zD4G2V3xKs0Caw\u003d\u003d","answers":["further planet","far planet","furthest planet","more far planet"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19s5sDpqQL6UhupnYx+xRBxfKt1L45nRsEKXiETj3k6BJBHPBf4BWEhymo1O0Glmap6fnXQTiY/BYlGQgcli04WLbHBHJTI9DyaT9dtfqWCdgJoWfWFWfDZhwogk8SckNU0zY9vPnopVA3H7UMT+sEJ1kQPvUOeE49QufkSW2GEUFtDxwZa6ohcTqr66jPsTiLZaq0iUFOERcYi8IN3iKNtRx3Rfs9Kq79pGuXbzcvqZLhTXXIduMsHRMdQFWxkPKlfN8UExAvCwtOODsvXgLvWfWU/xmwMILVQA07STA1ZvBP2GePEbCj4Ph0JhD0Cudy75n56uCIOn8TxYqLKnikSFEQbaFsmvfyQ79WFJGQ6VER+t7GWwa2ClsVXoIP+cS9WfqxO4TBQNVNeavIf3AgtTVkBr52FsBWONBold3rkR6GSYFXD0rrhAz+Mugvr+eKak0kKlR3DbqI2+0YbH8RUrr5ejLpG5OS8BEvL9R+G4V2EieWIkdzO1doCsRRTTZ91xYlw5s4hYb2Og8OOptDo6FPaKc7uPUAih12rggPyztXegrUyuJnv8kBuw2JpMQlMO7jY1mkBTaYKndJxknDE\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20032","langCode":"en","question":"0pjTQrRPFC9ZsQsr4OCiSb9Zo6xUwW8myojIzqWW/myOwtNh2x51Csxdm8voSkkbVofPMQ2ezyi1DdB8kGV7mw\u003d\u003d","answers":["the bigger","more big","bigger","the biggest"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/auVuJ8yYv2SW3yzd5Oo4LV3RwUWcg/Wmq43F7nCWRTaQfwwrmt5v4XtzIJQpPCIENCS9kvPe3JYcddSa6FXe/OrygMJ4Na+aAGY7sNHbjrhHWkpU7s5iKACUUSNSo+cR15ZyO7vTBuePnldmr7y9dlC+Fixiy3wP7G40CiiCS2209KeA2CWr1VlfvYPvdCmjh8ja7gAdUC9DFqTpcSWJCb+LpYIW0TH+5Rwj9v04tIA915MhnD+AlBWTtpn8xdGDcLcpxEFFcN9K1YQVtAuurzNiyP5oUp5TJJPKkHh55Ap1xmQqlHQTb4JM1YbN7UK7aKK77j7IiR0HlKwJuXaHLLRle/6Y1FfLyD17Db/qLFYca8GQLaIzx1mAAN3nnnutqYQWGrQDlLw9W7YIyMQGc\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20033","langCode":"en","question":"t7mbG3kGtRDzr3rcSSd1Sai4KdFolGTB3tAIVJiNgl+dVRKAluSFqLeRtnjfzV5dOFJXMorae5Iygko40Za1bg\u003d\u003d","answers":["the less harmful","less harmful","the least harmful","the more harmful"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+6JEi6bp/XnOUACbeO0E8BsKSEL4brPnhx5MwKXLNLspkDcHo0rxDx4hR3jZCFqQ2yVKox/q5FlIKs1uU5M4eQaggqR7PybC7V9adlIRuunjlutQTkGdymH+1K0V3hwi6V6FdHsxXaf1QyKDN8KTKz5KfcNPrTJ6o2aqjY/gEYG5HlCBf+tlG0gcIcl8CkfdBvCuPbMuuHgh3yTtf/WcST4KKmpkIZtPvoBT+m6Jz2QmzOYhzxrTEdHELmHZQ+6IFSpSzfEPRjRWICYhhSYi91LDiG3XEED+1UA5+ufi4t9X29akeuVDNjU6LO7PdJGBnxlXlQZ7WDi/RolXOMJNoXSj7OzxTItocDRcCpo0j64GQiN4XjgQeOSVdaoj8v8vojPuHbEHaEYbohWvI+xk9U\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20034","langCode":"en","question":"3XkjnjJAKDO8G0MU0cPyG4vW8SsK2aGy7b3aj+AkJalJ+FXfsXv3AfUt9NbLMV6dIrE3zyIV7S0TGM0OdhVJSw\u003d\u003d","answers":["less useful","as useful","more useful","most useful"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19j2letw8YUoLimKvoi1pylcawdNhgqlno2Pjg6VrpjxaQfwwrmt5v4XtzIJQpPCIENCS9kvPe3JYcddSa6FXe/OrygMJ4Na+aAGY7sNHbjrhHWkpU7s5iKACUUSNSo+cR15ZyO7vTBuePnldmr7y9dlC+Fixiy3wP7G40CiiCS2209KeA2CWr1VlfvYPvdCmjh8ja7gAdUC9DFqTpcSWJCb+LpYIW0TH+5Rwj9v04tIA915MhnD+AlBWTtpn8xdGDcLcpxEFFcN9K1YQVtAuurzNiyP5oUp5TJJPKkHh55Ap1xmQqlHQTb4JM1YbN7UK7aKK77j7IiR0HlKwJuXaHLLRle/6Y1FfLyD17Db/qLFYca8GQLaIzx1mAAN3nnnutqYQWGrQDlLw9W7YIyMQGc\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20035","langCode":"en","question":"8MeXJAB/Zse4Jd1OwLCusepA+rhQg9ESP/2Oe25MJ8Lr93gzfAMGAWTW09WmE+K6kQYrhTRpHs0eof99yp0s6Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["less popular","so popular","more popular","most popular"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11g3NoSaYaO6gSkxfGy7FWzN0p2HKHL1qDAKo23OMSSxZ0mXPwpY4ILDePAg2OvG+ph2czcHXlHAn1UayT66qYANOSMCkGA07fr7g5b8Vy4ZwBGk6MCVVJ46GnpQ/NMeRxd29LQsyvMv2KDvL2Fa8528PkokEaEEMnW/7O06zV3Vd02RedgaVhCVnc+p6t6obFQin0/2PmuUTVYJNBgmy/pvE31zo/4AOEq1cEZRTZUM5iSk0/hsACEfyJsoU5ApG76VcRlXlisZpqf7ZFhFNw86FPaKc7uPUAih12rggPyzlw1abCJqEEMK7OJZ8fnmnv6GQt8Gwn5IvI/OHaxKFHQ70WQqGXat7cEwuFju6yGZlx+oygjnAgTnzFy+9F1Q4BJUyfJJhtJB9bLnYOoxSBc\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20036","langCode":"en","question":"b6poBkk7s4/+irGIRGiGONWXf4iBLjZxQN8cN76GZ+s\u003d","answers":["hotter and hot","more and more hot","hotter and more hot","hotter and hotter"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zPV3o5TjI6UZKHhvGfwzTVIiVmmqd8rubpezMWyUL9GLvNuSIDjE6wod5txsEwjtzfKbhU2avKXYqwABieuTLfpM9/gJ5JBl3OAWwthWoo+nPAYrveJkXjl3h/FQPnRiOjRSV0XI8hYlDU4N+l58i2wgxC2PmII7FTwHQGyFy8g51pneVJ7S4jFaJxKDF7CFSfSj6Q2X0Bs0oh/s8UfhS+UFYXNbPV69mfaNnquoEiBqI/dsRO1PVPEuHu2WZt9Zvn2uW2s8Wi6ZEyCQCTplldF2KIhwcVUnIXr6V8+zz72RcrQjEyKPORxXzgBfT6RmeJYLVk2ZgoLxK0/Pk5XYsnnysYQpXuOJLoHXEAFJ71FVKlLN8Q9GNFYgJiGFJiL3dkzF573pX7tOlgPPfwoSV6OKuR1dW1hsuJG9xX5pK5VhxLKKpq2sMz8agvpMuApbA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20037","langCode":"en","question":"4Ooaglgj7RGvLz+qh4zujCjI4c1v8eIn3Px7MSjQxgwPMmFCnG84HMo1CrFxDGok","answers":["more interested and interested","more and less interested","more and more interested","interested and more interested"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15RMcEn+D9Q+gNdorqMwAavfDMs2m+sVVMrmQ2KNqajIVFBUZ5pgg2FNTmBhw9SMDsKOLS8wYBizntAkF85D/J6czmp0dQNdU6KtDrHhTDhUNR/rbRBgMhCSYUtAxwIJ4BtKgTZ2qBMSHBQ7UZ/xopoSHKSAzsCXlj3+OjtQ6Z3qRhpgEhv4bTXiZVypkPTKMII9rTGzTzpeN1oVaRC67LN9orJKndQ++f4SKdiSBcPn+lIkX1eh4halSmCRqmb+r1kqmwmmKO6Kk0M4YundLm+H0mu9jmA/mDOdDW8rSNQDqqt7ggCJ02r0L4rAYmS3IKH1m/YChZ3/08msUghJIVx+WU1lV7bWWp3hgpTddaCn28x2Rgl7fB4uQoozHx+oQ0nD823GvqH/Gh6TECTxwy8NDjhg+gjuyVELk4nye3f12phBYatAOUvD1btgjIxAZw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20038","langCode":"en","question":"a7j3OwgOjz2vwXjcifT/z9DnKOvCMG7i2qEE4T29rhe7ZQWGWzEnuMgA7JRDTY0+","answers":["more dark/colder","dark/cold","darker/ less cold","darker/ colder"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x10fCmgku4e1YoiQU1SWVgVo3qrBeRxJTIauNUYCogAIR7FhagzFCzVC5BSAFrKQVtFk0ID9tHsREM35YvXhVf1n+32FKtMAT5/a85LpCKe3rSZr/D1UnZGI1zHESY8WH7ZdLUL4bzg33bW7HyWhJwJ/p13HSIxZorKNyyjCrQMuR7SSGErkdUK1PbR8NGEfpRDy1E+a8ez5mAzRVXC5otePN6A7QhaYAWNTPxX4DC8pQQ8Cc+ZPwc4gE53UNgrf50xfuL5bCCrixr83juzthfwd21xBoJGfc49f4wYhfw/c9XHVmdS/JWtb9LTxhX847mf3IzW962vrGg+wiLJvpW0Qfu6jztL5P+/oNZJCiNXSa"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20039","langCode":"en","question":"2hHj0/eSxTYxu+ipJ55mKrLoy2dfxAmPABbvSFs0KHolP/ANlhXD4Wz5cy0APG5JekCTc+VuCY/HPKgGBhzZP1FO+gAU1NCyFZhWxTNuC+iEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["kinder/less generous","kinder/more generous","kind/more generous","kinder/ generous"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15juuSP3oK2HqnPF75bMxjVvHY41buwb4DjiHC2lMhS2WsRXPpiiZoN6gZrzJxG++vMPlQXAu0xuVDhwVMNTRmh9Ms6YL1hNkdKvAYCNFkEGFnbGd5uuVjwcPfkdcWaQbU5IfKekoPA68p2FX3gfD0Rr0fzdFfNNaGZT7lQ4412JdFpJbD3SVpXSPBN8kCCYsZO6vx7AaraWzFgTbpCNePi6iek6wyztNaPPbnKX9mvfbJUqjH+rkWUgqzW5Tkzh5M4tKl/KprMYl0GNomLeI2S7nPga10x/Se/qjJFBT3dBYQBfUHFiFUWw/OHuSMVl07lMcuBilq3DejZKtql0oBTgP3kd/gGwskUDDARhjkL+27uQD2Hk5j9DQcLr//nEyw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20040","langCode":"en","question":"z2m0XNrBUydJZLNs1qwwOKpPG3OStKT6Nhbnzk/nO37bShGzNRCipUTM8jG6MW6u","answers":["fashionable/more attractive","more fashionable/more attractive","fashionable/attractive","more fashionable/attractive"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wGgWt6+tlgDVM5dgTiDz2zz2MGQNI+VOzotPI9IxUKvVkNL1R+41PVOgVyuifhdwv1lTpkWRKl13Ax71iY0bmMZ3jdf5fLQFlf/nTGcebRCsktj3P4N1IbJ4/Pqa6xeXPEUNdABYMftI4MBpJJNYwIZQLNUndy7XUYGldGlofsoc/Tzdsq/X48uukXxq8hUVlPx2orm1wEXPzQnZGFY/6lgfBYbSZNO6SW/pKcNjw9qAQJXoznRqDEanXa3i7wrtdXZrMJR0bq29Msp1Ttfai70HgT0ztcMBNTStOZ/ZlPXLj0V2ARCdnQP8ZhB2zuwlI7GLc7ntla+dnALQOtTUj1HIS1axceTajjSj+7wTJVL4hmukGdQWKruGDsGzsd2iR+7qPO0vk/7+g1kkKI1dJo\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20041","langCode":"en","question":"w7967AiNF8D5WhPUvh7AcCc/w0C/WHKW1uotdu35lpm0Eqh3UsGMHagLUWar90znd6wVZS53bl/Y8DHdZVORkA\u003d\u003d","answers":["complicated/less interested","more complicated/interested","complicated/ interested","more complicated/less interested"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11zKnojsNEhBM8JzvwZTNnutJwHWGeSrVWieebvQX03Qd3O+IxvW8ewVJmJMMHzw6v1lTpkWRKl13Ax71iY0bmMZ3jdf5fLQFlf/nTGcebRCsktj3P4N1IbJ4/Pqa6xeXPEUNdABYMftI4MBpJJNYwIZQLNUndy7XUYGldGlofsoc/Tzdsq/X48uukXxq8hUVlPx2orm1wEXPzQnZGFY/6lgfBYbSZNO6SW/pKcNjw9qAQJXoznRqDEanXa3i7wrtdXZrMJR0bq29Msp1Ttfai70HgT0ztcMBNTStOZ/ZlPXLj0V2ARCdnQP8ZhB2zuwlI7GLc7ntla+dnALQOtTUj1HIS1axceTajjSj+7wTJVL4hmukGdQWKruGDsGzsd2iR+7qPO0vk/7+g1kkKI1dJo\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20042","langCode":"en","question":"GInwLlWCNpwNQkSV+uwsyQLdz7wAQRiTjGErY1JKn+r4wdPLqPaRiNubkO03Aj8VCgHFa1EDfLHghPZYTXMq3A\u003d\u003d","answers":["using","to be used","use","to use"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x118gBWc2Ru+z5adj3nAihMMLgGTLjgMYqhCFR5etaf6HMi7K24OHeEs1RkPhC2azp6JBa6xlIeXiu45EvUXyUizgWTo72lQscws7dGlLN2aaxIOFg+jjRSfUj4c2SchoI9e61l3xyYXfEmnZgpSDhmu8dRiXMfXRXqWI+0emFwGjp4O4iyWGUIrpQB+BJblaNtVSIOnzhfLORLoMO8gcdQuRrq8mWLeFQzDEmAlezlBTF+tVXwPOZg/EZyxrWPn6y944wou5vUTxgD1WXypEalqJ1VWwJHX8G6AaHBVwZEr1mn6QZ311s8XJylCGeCICWQEjTLCQ+nmJhC8pvIvQ6QCu9LfAMZXM5CJMIxHyF+NUg47NHPX0ZKluvmL4C+W7L61gBS7SRsZ38HLnyb3DOqtV4HQcOaItdDObB5UsN+pSkzsrFG5gkOHJHwkThWVz5lX7TOr/SYXlbHYEZxQBJu0yQNWHYk+ABwiCoNCgj94rKDPXmcBDHULbPhF7cCmDATsTRODqMVeudie5h2NBDgAEHrQrPVO8izpjPKZMcEjy"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20043","langCode":"en","question":"FHY83cNnFihA0q/cjizTZ7v999FOFKKCy5AJP/HKAT/tSdwVxYFKu5DzOArzY0UhVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["two years","two year older","two years older","two older"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zb1K3cCsumm6FEnsuBxQ6GR5h4xqfAcNFC80mShpw8DcKSzaZsQbybZVPjBhZo51PxLqwjlWM5hraAv5X23ePmdkk7F9wEOWOWO8AKxI0nMPmZpdJnVy94Xq+F9kYrAP4FWOq/kHPvKonfTUxTfrCPAG51AD3WCouk2FDiBJZvotVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20044","langCode":"en","question":"Qr52aSqqcJ5hkPDHxnBqIgrqD3IWBd3N5NNfCTlbvO5RVf8ZMRClxylOEnUenXRU","answers":["three as much as","three times much than","three times as much as","three times as much than"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18R5rXHNhAI3NlUjMMsAswchcSeeDlLA8VtKm6myjt/zUnxkiO0hkDmsPxnKtM40W4kiWB5m3k82kc1gcOkIst0GerZW0Chj/lmN1uuMCKtQsH83x+9hr9g+x1enTUNnsyrf5RpsRFGIxzmydOGz2peMMH7VyfSuLc8HfhlEyIhoLZ1pTIfNwBEAOIcga/IDlQFUOdprkM6vcLUQwTaH9pr2heDiNbzFSefFrSwjzU9EYuDCqS/WOo0xtMMA6UMwFQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20045","langCode":"en","question":"4zg+WIpo1uupFPL+2HtWfaR5VE5u8cdyV1JpmD+h++JUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["twice as many craps than","twice as many craps as","two many craps as","two as many craps as"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12efg03O8Zr45HH3JgrBP0/on59trZ3LBV5l8Bjd6sghsX7HPtLP7djXmScZmC4FtXiW8y+C2RGcpQrEsYoBzQpkpQBZqVeD9huAGTEIl7wwtoDIFQABUcQGrnSIDKPZPByQBEB6SzJ1WsVcXGbna8JpjCkofAQNfXXqrcWuKVrWpbC2aKxwbPz72eMERevENfj6SrbcyJe5kvGwAY+cuARYcTriLg2fqknL5LLwZym/OEPNluZDvdIdqGF2heoCSA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20046","langCode":"en","question":"+HIOR9kNbdFeKk9QqlidJ6ta7UiFojfz694UvWMl2kI\u003d","answers":["less apples","fewer apples","few apples","least apples"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x181vYSApvVI4YVQhFO4KS41uLg7TU+uMiwgGVsycSehV027qe8RPeB5/lI49o8FsxMQsZa2tp89MdKMw36xsVAtLfuOb8SeLxUfEmgqUMdqaN9Y8iQzdcRMF50/KQBuN1GOZ9KhqzmEEZ8k7pRpWvT2++l6Bmp9rBtlaMHlZslKMQdyWTbniBwccbE06yH3JCg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20047","langCode":"en","question":"LciKtYtre4OfCTVsXu1Zgx1YlcmYX3UCUq4xO41IJJk\u003d","answers":["fewer","less free time","few","least"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zKTwx/Bp2x/XJLGzr4NlNyFZV/SAAoyMkDnLBj/Y59B3LdjtuBNacmzCcBErfapwG73FDGpUsDK7rTsWv+QW71kKOh5+Y4jfhpp0/REXSJin6fU7D+tk1wiWg+0jYL8nvvHZG+26RqBbZd9qkLDHfZVtWE1lM5YIeiEpaVFu8Mhq1q2zi/IHgKVgEbc8OmUV7EktUBqd4Br6/ZPMd0Hiic\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20048","langCode":"en","question":"1p80LWkZuFMlG+GdG/rgADhdln6oCq9DzB3RnkzbIrJYGnDcG/VJcBj77XI4zcQ2","answers":["more and less people","more and more person","few and few","more and more people"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15RMcEn+D9Q+gNdorqMwAavcBLUfhrODsDI0pAC9VCg+PUTwZIt5AJiTrSU+gp5MgneMzPj2zaxz5S5/iAOXNdHChcC8Bn8ZCp4/nF3+OinN5uIZwr4kh9qju/F5uCGm71lic4fm7ZxwkRCeBs0hjFa1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20049","langCode":"en","question":"iFrd/pRZZvJ2fqWYhtwMgoXrVfeygRMSW8aiMhlfllI\u003d","answers":["few and less students","less and more students","few and few students","less and less students"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zs/p/gmG1pvA952OpvdKSAOrKmkbyTXgZUNc77AS70KsX7HPtLP7djXmScZmC4FtXiW8y+C2RGcpQrEsYoBzQpzjYmwltF3gka99NHaeW+wDq6D6N14mjDrud0T4RTa/NlINhmG2O9DkGQqJC5ve7Jz/gc4FczL4aZAKl6TH1Mn"}]